When I play, I can do amazing things.
I can run, I can jump, and I'm still learning to do more.
Special Olympics Young Athletes help young children around the world discover their abilities
and develop their strengths through the power of sport and play.
Young Athletes introduces basic sport skills like kicking and throwing through fun activities
to children with and without intellectual disabilities ages 2 to 7.
Children of all ability levels participate and they all benefit.
They develop important motor skills, grow stronger, build confidence at every milestone,
and learn to interact and communicate with others.
Family share in the fun and learn to support their child's development.
And everyone learns acceptance and friendship.
With activities in more than 125 countries, Young Athletes reach children around the world.
Giving families, communities, and schools the tools to create inclusive environments
and help children of all abilities unlock their potential and envision brighter hopes
for the future.
I loved to play.
It makes me happy to play with friends and it helps me be the best I can be.
So come on, let's play together.